Raymond Spilman Papers
Raymond Spilman Papers
- Books
  - Hultgren, Ken / The Art of Animal Drawing McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc.: 1950 (Box 3)
  - Lafarge, Oliver / A Pictorial History of the American Indian Crown Publishers, Inc., New York: 1956 (Box 3)
  - Vlaviano, Basil J. / George Constant Arts, Inc., New York: 1961 (Box 4)
  - Schmeckebier, Laurence E. / John Steuart Curry’s Pageant In America American Artists Group, New York: 1943 (Box 4)
  - Sloane, Patricia / Color: Basic Principles, New Directions Studio Vista Ltd.: 1968 (Box 4)
  - Letraset Letraset USA, Inc.: 1976 (Box 4)
  - Whitehill, Clayton / The Moods of Type Barnes and Nobles, Inc., New York: 1947 (Box 4)
  - Typositor poster (Box 4)
  - Format and Formaline Catalog No. 6 Graphic Products Corporation (Box 4)
  - Texture plates, The Akron Metal Etching Co. (Box 4)
  - Flexwood wood samples (Box 4)
  - Salutes, Alcoa / The Bauhaus Alcoa (Box 4)
  - Hornung, Clarence P. / Antique Automobiles Dover Publications, Inc., New York: 1971, coloring book (Box 4)
  - The Science of Color Optical Society of America: 1953 (Box 4)
  - Itten, Johannes / The Elements of Color Van Nostrand Reinhold Company: 1974 (Box 4)
  - Lewis, W.S. / Selected Letters of Horace Walpole Yale University Press, New Haven, CT: 1973 (Box 4)
  - The Structurist The Structurist: 1973/ 1974 (Box 4)
  - Billmeyer, Fred W. Jr. / AIC Annotated Bibliography on Color Order Systems Mimeoform Services, Inc.: 1977 (Box 4)
  - Art Direction Advertising Trade Publications: 1974, magazine, annotated (Box 4)
  - Westraco Inspirations 213, Westraco Quality Press: 1960 (Box 4)
  - Smithsonian magazine, August 1977 (Box 4)
  - Print magazine, May/June 1969 (Box 4)
  - Taillander, Yvon / Claude Monet Crown Publishers, Inc.: 1967 (Box 4)
  - Fry, Roger / Seurat Phaidon Publishers Inc.: 1965 (Box 4)
  - Mendelwitz, Daniel M. / A History of American Art Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., New York: 1960 (Box 4)
  - Arguelles, Jose A. / Charles Henry and the Formation of a Psychophysical Aesthetic The University of Chicago Press, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Mathey, Francois / The Impressionists Frederick A. Praeger, Inc.: 1961 (Box 4)
  - Wurmfeld, Sanford / Color Documents: A Presentational Theory Hunter College Art Gallery: 1985 (Box 4)
  - Blake, Peter / God’s Own Junkyard Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., New York: 1964 (Box 5)
  - Products That Teach Armco, Middleton, OH: 1980 (Box 5)
  - Hornung, Clarence Pearson / Handbook of Design and Devices Dover Publications, New York: 1932 (Box 5)
  - Hardware Arts from Drawing Board to Marketplace 1980, catalog (Box 5)
  - Capitman, Barbara Baer / American Trademark Design Dover Publications, Inc., New York / 1976 (Box 5)
  - Industrial Design and Aesthetics Bradda Printing Service, Ottawa: 1978, seminar catalog (Box 5)
  - Eames, Charles and Ray / Images of Early America Herman Miller, Inc.: 1976, includes personal letter (Box 5)
  - Papanek, Victor and James Hennessey / How Things Don’t Work Pantheon Books, New York: 1977 (Box 5)
  - Knoblaugh, Ralph R. / Modeling for Industrial Design McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc.: 1958 (Box 5)
  - Rogers, Meyric R. / Italy at Work: Her Renaissance in Design Today The Compagnia Nazionale Artigiana, Italy (Box 5)
  - Barker, Alfred F. / Ornamentation and Textile Design Frederick A. Stokes Company (Box 5)
  - Gestaltete Industrieform in Deutschland Verlag gmbh, Dusseldorf: 1954, signed copy (Box 5)
  - Schroeder, Francis de N. Anatomy for Interior Designers and How to talk to a Client Whitney Publications, Inc., New York: 1948 (Box 5)
  - O’Hara, Frank / New Spanish Painting and Sculpture The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1960 (Box 5)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York Painting and Sculpture Acquisitions January 1, 1961 through December 31, 1961 The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1962 (Box 5)
  - Schmeckebier, Laurence / Zoltan Sepeshy: Forty Years of His Work Syracuse University, Syracuse, NY: 1966 (Box 5)
  - American Printmakers 1964 Syracuse University, Syracuse, NY: 1964 (Box 5)
  - Selz, Peter / The Work of Jean Dubuffet The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1962 (Box 5)
  - Selz, Peter / Mark Rothko The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1961 (Box 5)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York Painting and Sculpture Acquisitions January 1, 1960 through December 31, 1960 The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1961 (Box 5)
  - Kahn, Louis I. / Richards Medical Research Building The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1961 (Box 5)
  - Stone, Irving / The Story of Michelangelo’s Pieta Doubleday and Company, Inc.: 1964 (Box 5)
  - Soby, James Thrall / Yves Tanguy The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1955 (Box 5)
  - Dreyfus, Henry / Industrial Design Volume 5 Comet Press, Inc.: 1957 (Box 5)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / Industrial Design A Progress Report: 1929-1952 Davis, Delaney, Inc. (Box 5)
  - Kelly, Kenneth L. and Deane B. Judd / Color and Dictionary of Names U.S. Department of Commerce: 1976 (Box 5)
  - Birren, Faber / Light, Color, and Environment Schiffer Publishing Ltd., 1988, autographed (Box 5)
  - Distribution Age magazine, June 1949 (Box 5)
  - Legman, G. / The Art of Mahlon Blaine Peregrine Books: 1982 (Box 5)
  - Propst, Robert / The Office: A Facility Based on Change The Business Press: 1968 (Box 5)
  - Dot Zero Dot Zero Incorporated (Box 5)
  - Wessel, Joan and Nada Westerman / American Design Classics Design Publications: 1985 (Box 5)
  - Dreyfus, Henry / Designing for People Simon and Schuster, Inc.: 1955 (Box 5)
  - Osborn on Leisure Ridge Press, Inc.: 1957 (Box 5)
  - Craig, Edward Gordon / Towards A New Theatre E.P. Dutton and Company, Inc.: 1913 (Box 5)
  - Post, Dan / The Classic Cord Dan R. Post Publications: 1952 (Box 6)
  - Brown, Curtis F. / Star-Spangled Kitsch Universe Books: 1975 (Box 6)
  - Pevsner, Nikolaus / Pioneers of Modern Design Penguin Books: 1960 (Box 6)
  - Hobhouse, Christopher / 1851 and the Crystal Palace E.P. Dutton and Company, Inc.: 1937 (Box 6)
  - Taylor, Pamela / The Notebooks of Leonardo da Vinci Mentor Books: 1960 BOX 6 (cont.): (Box 6)
  - Browne, Baker and Frank Lloyd Wright / Architecture and Modern Life Harper and Brothers Publishers: 1937 (Box 6)
  - Osborne on Leisure Ridge Press: 1957 (Box 6)
  - Schroeder, Joseph J. Jr. / 1908 Sears, Roebuck Catalogue No. 117: A Treasured Replica for the Archives of History The Gun Digest Company: 1971 (Box 6)
  - STC Stamford Type (in binder), Stamford Typesetting Company (Box 6)
  - The Plastic Letters and Numerals Condensed Catalog Scott Plastics, Co.: 1973 (Box 6)
  - Stein, Ralph / The Great Cars Ridge Press, Inc.: 1967 (Box 6)
  - Angelucci, Enzo and Alberto Bellucci / The Automobile: From Steam to Gasoline McGraw-Hill Book Company: 1974 (Box 6)
  - Industrial Design In America 1954 Farrar, Straus and Young, Inc.: 1954 (Box 6)
  - Groner, Alex / The American Heritage History of American Business and Industry American Heritage Publishing Company, Inc.: 1972 (Box 6)
  - Neilson, Katherine B. / Selected Paintings and Sculptures From the Yale University Art Gallery Yale University Press: 1972 (Box 6)
  - Inter-Society Color Council, envelope. contains notes (Box 6)
  - Adam, Ansel and Nancy Newhall / This Is the American Earth Sierra Club, San Francisco: 1960 (Box 6)
  - Projections in Steel United States Steel: 1962 (Box 7)
  - Art Across America The Mead Corporation (Box 7)
  - Recent Painting USA: The Figure The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1962 (Box 7)
  - Bush, Martin H. / Ben Shahn: The Passion of Sacco and Vanzetti Syracuse University, Syracuse, NY: 1968 (Box 7)
  - Bush, Martin H. / American Political Cartoons: 1865-1965 Syracuse University, Syracuse, NY: 1966 (Box 7)
  - O’Hara, Frank / Nakian The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1966 (Box 7)
  - Soby, James Thrall / Juan Gris The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1958 (Box 7)
  - Chrysler Art Museum of Provincetown / Inaugural Exhibition Chrysler Art Museum of Provincetown, MA: 1958 (Box 7)
  - Ritchie, Andrew Candruff / Edouard Vuillard The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1954 (Box 7)
  - A Guide to the Tate Gallery Tate Gallery Publication Dept.: 1963 (Box 7)
  - Pierre Lesieut: November 17-December 2, 1970 Imp. Union Paris: 1970 (Box 7)
  - Maurice Rianchon: October 27 – November 14, 1970 Imp. Union Paris: 1970 (Box 7)
  - Twentieth Century Engineering The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1964, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Frank, Klaus / Exhibitions Frederick A. Praeger: 1961 (Box 7)
  - Abbott, Bernice / Changing New York E.P. Dutton and Company, Inc.: 1939 (Box 7)
  - Nelson, George / Storage Whitney Publications, Inc.: 1954 (Box 7)
  - Innovative I Engineering Polymers Boeing Commercial Airplane Company: 1986 (Box 7)
  - Arends, Mark / Product Rendering With Markers Van Nostrand Reinhold Company: 1984, autographed (Box 7)
  - Sutnar, Ladislav / Package Design: The Force of Visual Selling Arts, Inc.: 1953 (Box 7)
  - McAndrew, John / Guide to Modern Architecture Northeast States The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1940 (Box 7)
  - Fabbro, Mario Dal / Furniture for Modern Interiors Reinhold Publishing Company: 1954 (Box 7)
  - Premio Compasso d’oro 1964 (Box 7)
  - 1900-1986 Mobili, arrendi, oggetti vari Idea Books Edizioni: 1986 (Box 7)
  - Design in Finland The Finnish Foreign Trade Association: 1992 (Box 7)
  - Art Deco The Minneapolis Institute of Arts: 1971 (Box 7)
  - Koch, Rudolf / The Book of Signs Dover Publications, Inc.: 1930 (Box 7)
  - The Brentano Collection of Sculpture Masterpieces in Replica Brentano’s, Inc.: 1955 (Box 7)
  - Longstreet, Stephen and Ethel / Man of Montmartre Signet Book: 1958 (Box 7)
  - House Beautiful magazine, April 1953 (Box 8)
  - Color The Knapp Press: 1980 (Box 8)
  - Jones, Tom Douglas / The Art of Light and Color Van Nostrand Reinhold Company: 1972 (Box 8)
  - Folge, Funfle / Farbige Raumkunst Julius Haffmann Verlag, Struttgart: 1929 (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Fridolf / The Illustrations of Rockwell Kent Dover Publications, Inc., New York: 1975 (Box 8)
  - Flynn, Spencer, Martyniuk, and Hendrick / Interim Report: The Effects of Light in Human Judgement and Behavior Illuminating Engineering Research Institute, New York: August 1975 (Box 8)
  - Federal Standard No. 595a, Colors (Box 8)
  - Knife/Fork/Spoon Walker Art Center, Minneapolis: 1951 (Box 8)
  - Kennedy, John F. et. al. / Creative America The Ridge Press: 1962 (Box 8)
  - The Stieglitz Circle Whitney Museum of American Art: 1992 (Box 8)
  - Real Livingwood Veneer Wall Covering Wall Coverings of Merit Co. (Box 8)
  - Holme, Geoffrey / Industrial Design and the Future The Studio Publications, Inc.: 1934 (Box 8)
  - Szarkowski, John / The Photographer’s Eye The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1965 (Box 8)
  - Seitz, William C. / Mark Tobey The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1959 (Box 8)
  - Miller, Dorothy C. / Sixteen Americans The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1959 (Box 8)
  - Pinchot, Ben / Female Form Bridgman Publishers, Inc.: 1935 (Box 8)
  - Elsen, Albert E. / Rodin The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1963 (Box 8)
  - The New American Painting As Shown in Eight European Countries 1958-1959 The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1959 (Box 8)
  - Ambaz, Emilio / Italy: The New Domestic Landscape: Achievements and Problems of Italian Design The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1973 (Box 8)
  - Taylor, Joshua C. / Futurism The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1961 (Box 8)
  - Saarien, Eliel / Search for Form: A Fundamental Approach to Art Reinhold Publishing Corporation: 1948 (Box 8)
  - Santos, Reynoldo dos Santos / Nuno Goncalves Phaidon Publishers, Inc.: 1955 (Box 8)
  - Box: Duplicate Material for Additional Yellow Books (Box 8)
  - Box: Duplicate Material for Additional Yellow Books (Box 9)
  - Box: Duplicate Material for Additional Yellow Books (Box 9)
  - More Business / The Science of Color: A Summary of the Theories of Dr. Wilhelm Ostwald American Photo-Engravers Association: 1937 (Box 9)
  - Chevreul, M.E. / The Principles of Harmony and Contrast of Color and their Applications to the Arts Schiffer Publishing, Ltd.: 1987, signed copy (Box 9)
  - Birren, Faber / History of Color in Painting Litton Educational Publishing, Ltd.: 1965 (Box 9)
  - Rubin, William / Pablo Picasso: A Retrospective The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1980 (Box 9)
  - Leymarie, Jean / Impressionism Editions d’Art Albert Skira: 1955 (Box 9)
  - Dibner, Berin / Leonardo Da Vinci Machines and Weaponry McGraw-Hill Book Company, New York: 1974 (Box 9)
  - Of, For, and By Georgia O’Keeffe Whitney Museum of American Art: 1994 (Box 9)
  - Spilman, Raymond / RSID Raymond Spilman Industrial Design: 1979 (Box 9)
  - Kent, Rockwell / World-Famous Paintings Wise & Co., Inc., New York: 1939 (Box 10)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy / Language of Vision Paul Theobald: 1944 (Box 10)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy / Structure in Art and In Science George Braziller, New York: 1965 (Box 10)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy / Education of Vision George Braziller, New York: 1965 (Box 10)
  - Mobilia No. 140, Mobilia, Denmark: 1967 (Box 10)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy / The Nature and Art of Motion George Braziller, New York: 1965 (Box 10)
  - Reti, Ladislao and Bern Dibner / Leonardo da Vinci Technologist Burndy Library, Inc.: 1969 (Box 10)
  - A Look at Architecture Visitors Center, Columbus, Indiana: 1974 (Box 10)
  - Design Forecast 2 Aluminum Company of America: 1960 (Box 10)
  - Chamberlain, Samuel / The New England Image Hasting House, Publishers, Inc.: 1962 (Box 10)
  - Barr, Alfred H. Jr. / Masters of Modern Art The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1954 (Box 10)
  - Selz, Peter / New Images of Man The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1959 (Box 10)
  - Ritchie, Andrew Carnduff / The New Decade: 22 European Painters and Sculptors The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1955 (Box 10)
  - Haftmann, Werner et. Al. / German Art of the Twentieth Century The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1957 (Box 10)
  - Odilon Redon, Gustave Moreau, Rodolphe Bresdin The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1961 (Box 10)
  - Soby, James Thrall / Arp The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1958 (Box 10)
  - International Exhibition of Photography: The Camera as Witness The Southam Printing Company Limited: 1967 (Box 10)
  - Today and Tomorrow The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1960 (Box 10)
  - The Register of the Museum of Art Volume II, Number 7, The University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas: December 1961 (Box 10)
  - The Register of the Museum of Art Volume II, Number 8 The University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas: April 1962 (Box 10)
  - The Register of the Museum of Art Volume II, Number 4 The University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas: March 1960 (Box 10)
  - The Register of the Museum of Art Volume II, Number 5 The University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas: December 1960 (Box 10)
  - The Register of the Museum of Art Volume II, Number 6 The University of Kansas, Lawrence, Kansas: June 1961 (Box 10)
  - The Image of Lost and Found Institute of Contemporary Art: 1960 (Box 10)
  - Design from Scandinavia No. 4, Behrndt Bogtryk and Offset, Copenhagen, signed copy (Box 10)
- Tapes
  Number or letter in parenthesis is the item ID number, as assigned by the donor. Tapes are filed in the box in numeric order by ID number. Tapes are listed below in alphabetical order based on the name of the speaker (if known). Where the tape case had a title on the spine, that title was used; if there was no title on the spine, information was taken from the side labels. The information below is formatted as follows:
  ([item ID no]) [name of speaker, if known] / [title as written on the item] [date, if known]
  Access to tapes may require creation of a working copy. Please contact the repository for more information.
  - [unknown] / 6: [side notes are extensive but VERY hard to read], 5/10/82; Y (Box 92)
  - [unknown] / 7: [side notes are extensive but VERY hard to read], 12/5/82; Z (Box 92)
  - [unknown] / 8: [side notes are extensive but VERY hard to read], 12/5/82; Aa (Box 92)
  - [unknown] / 9: [side notes are extensive but VERY hard to read], 12/5/82; Bb (Box 92)
  - Alexander, James M. / James M. Alexander FIDSA bio for formative years of USID, 8/18/91; 079 (Box 92)
  - Bach, A. / A. Bach Jean Reinecke, 1969; 1979; 056 (Box 92)
    See also Bach, Alfons / Reinecke, Jean (1979) (tape 36)
  - Bach, Alfons / Alfons Bach 1969 formative yearsof USID (Hose), L (Box 92)
  - Bach, Alfons / Alfons Bach formative years i.D.H. orig. and trans to 60, 1969; 083; 2 copies (Box 92)
  - Bach, Alfons / Alfons Bach from 1920-69 formative years USID, K (Box 92)
  - Balmer, Jim / Jim Balmer IDSA, 02/91; 058 (Box 92)
  - BecVar, Arthur N. / “What Does A Design MGR Do?”, 002 (Box 92)
  - BecVar, Arthur N. / Art BecVar 3 of 3 "update" early years USID, 6/3/91; 077 (Box 92)
  - BecVar, Arthur N. / FIDSA General Electric Company, 1969; 001 (Box 92)
  - Blanc, Al / Al Blanc, undated; O (Box 92)
  - Borchot, Sidney / Sidney Borchot Louie A. - Ben Webster - Bix B. - Whitman Stardust - Louis - etc. [music], T (Box 92)
  - Braun, Francis F. / [no title on spine] Francis Braun Early years Cincinatti OH School Services - Post War To present, 124 (Box 92)
  - Bredendieck, Hin / early years, 093 (Box 92)
  - Bressler, Peter / Peter Bressler Invite to RS for ID Hist at Phila., 1976; 005 (Box 92)
  - Bruce, John / John Bruce copy of micro tapes, 1983; 069 (Box 92)
  - Chapman, Dave / Dave Chapman Tel. Interview IDH orig sent to Pulos, 12/28/77; 006 (Box 92)
  - Cooke, Alistair / 1918-1930 Alstar [sic] Cook comments very good, X (Box 92)
  - Cooke, Alistair / Alstaire [sic] Cooke Comments 1918-1930, W (Box 92)
  - Cooke, Alistair / Post WWI - US - Eng. comparison Alistair Cooke Masterpiece Theatre Pearl Bailey Classic with Bost. Pops, V (Box 92)
  - Crapsey, Arthur Hunt / Arthur Hunt Crapsey memories & stories early years USID, 2/12/91; 100 (Box 92)
  - Crapsey, Arthur Hunt / Arthur Hunt Crapsey memories & stories early years USID, 2/12/91; 101 (Box 92)
  - Cushing, George / George Cushing, 3/10/78; 007 (Box 92)
  - Dailey, Don / Don Dailey FIDSA IDH memories, 1/23/91; 098 (Box 92)
  - Dailey, Don / J. McLeod Little bio and anecdoate (case); Don Dailey FIDSA Memories (tape), 12/29/90; 052 (Box 92)
  - Deskey, D. / - End, 10/04/78; 009 (Box 92)
  - Deskey, D. / Original - Deskey - NYC, 10/04/78; 008 (Box 92)
  - Diffrient, Neils / Neils Diffrient on H Dreyfuss stories & memories, 059 (Box 92)
  - Diffrient, Niels / Neils Diffrient at Aspin [sic] [side note says "Orig. donated by Wayne Champion IDSA"], 2/1/92; N (Box 92)
  - Diffrient, Niels / Niels Diffrient Bio Notes Aspin [sic] B, 4/15/95; 2/1/92; N2 (Box 92)
  - Diffrient, Niels / Niels Diffrient bio part I & II for RS and FY of USID, 5/92; 123B; 2 copies (Box 92)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / H. D. Memorial NYC, 11/15/72; B (Box 92)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / H. Dreyfuss interview F.Y.I.D. - R. Spilman - Quotes to A V Hist., 8/12/68; 013 (Box 92)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / Henry Dreyfuss - Hose 15 min Side E open, 085 (Box 92)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / Henry Dreyfuss Memorial NYC w/Goldsmith, Hewitt, Jo Mezinger, Griffith, Nelson Formative years of USID, 11/15/73; 011 (Box 92)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / Thoughts on design Dreyfuss Teague, 065 (Box 92)
  - Ebstein, John / John Ebstein FYID Memories Loewy, etc., 2/1/91; 099 (Box 92)
  - Everrett, Julian / Julian Everett first partner - H. Dreyfuss, 6/7/78; C (Box 92)
  - Everrett, Julian / Julian Everett on H. Dreyfuss for formative years of USID, 6/7/78; D (Box 92)
  - Florian, Gordon / Gordon Florian the early years part 1 & 2, 8/10/83; 070 (Box 92)
  - Florian, Gordon / Gordon Florian the early years part 3 & 4, 8/10/83; 071 (Box 92)
  - Glass, Henry P. / Henry P. Glass interview WEEF by Ritchfield Memories of I.D., 6/3/81; 086 (Box 92)
  - Gruen, Robert / Robert Gruen R. Hose, Q (Box 92)
  - Gruen, Robert / Robert Gruen FIDSA memories 2, 2/8/86; 076 (Box 92)
  - Gruen, Robert / Robert Gruen Memories IDI/IDSA, 8/21/86; H (Box 92)
  - Gruen, Robert / Robert Gruene and wife FIDSA I.D.H. interview, 2/8/86; 076A (Box 92)
  - Hart, Rita / Rita Hart long time private secretary to H. Dreyfuss – interview on her last day at office, 017 (Box 92)
  - I.D. Memories / Dreyfuss Reinecke Jergenson Russel Wright Robt. Gruen, 1969; 066 (Box 92)
  - Jergenson, George / George Jergenson RSID Don McFarland, 1979; 057 (Box 92)
  - K—, R— / 3 & 4 R.K., 019 (Box 92)
  - K—, R— / R.K. 5 & 6, 020 (Box 92)
  - Karlen, Paul / [no title on spine] Paul Karlen Peter Muller-Munk Hist. of Petch Muller-Munk Assoc., 3/15/69; 120 (Box 92)
  - Kaufman, E. Jr. / A3 E. Kaufman by Pulos, 5/19/83; 125 (Box 92)
  - Kaufman, E. Jr. / E. Kaufman Jr. in his Apt 355 Park (Pulos) for USID Hist., 5/16/84; A (Box 92)
  - Keogh, Rita / Rita Keogh on Ruddy (D. 5-12-95 age 84) tel conversation, U (Box 92)
  - Kibble, Edward / Edward Kibble memories 60 years with W.D.Teague Part 3 4, 088K (Box 92)
  - Kibble, Edward / Edward Kibble WDTA Memories 5 6, 9/24/90; 090K (Box 92)
  - Kibble, Edward / Tape 1 & 2 E. Kibble interview memories, 8/22/90; 9/24/90; 087K (Box 92)
  - Kibble, Edward / WDTA Memories: NYC, 9/24/90; 089 (Box 92)
  - Koepp, R. / R. Koepp 8.7.78 & RS., 018 (Box 92)
  - Kostollow, Rowena / Lurelle Guild, 3/26/78; 126 (Box 92)
  - Kostollow, Rowena / Rowena Kostollow Interview by A. Pulos, 11/17/83; 060 (Box 92)
  - LA / [no title on spine or tape], I (Box 92)
  - Lamb, Tom / Tom Lamb 1 & 2 tel. partial conv. scientist designer dreamer, 2/11/76; 022 (Box 92)
  - Lamb, Tom / Tom Lamb 3/4, 2/27/76; 023 (Box 92)
  - Lamb, Tom / Tom Lamb Cont. 60, 026 (Box 92)
  - Lamb, Tom / Tom Lamb cont't 5 & 6, 3/76; 024 (Box 92)
  - Lamb, Tom / Tom Lamb interview 7 8, 3/76; 025 (Box 92)
  - Latham, Richard / Latham, Richard 103A - RS - RH, 1969; 127 (Box 92)
  - Latham, Richard / Richard L. Latham of IDSA Formative years U.S. Ind. Des., 1969; 027 (Box 92)
  - Lippincott, J. Gordan / J. Gordon Lippincott Early Years of ID Part 1 & 2 & 3, 09/21/78; 028 / 029 (Box 92)
  - Little, Jack / Jack Little 25 min also Paul Karlen, 7/29/91; 051 (Box 92)
  - Madawick, Tucker / Tucker Madawick, Apr 79; 032 (Box 92)
  - McAlistor, Paul / Paul MacAlister FIDSA Leon Gordon Miller (1969), 4/6/70(?); 055 (Box 92)
  - McConnell, B. / Barbara McConnell on P. McC. 0-250A Julian Everett Drey. Part 250A All of B, 050 (Box 92)
  - Meyers, C. Stowe / C. Stowe Meyers early years Chicago talk, 6/5/87; 078 (Box 92)
  - Meyers, Stowe / C. Stowe Meyers Chicago talk, 1987; 082 (Box 92)
  - Miller, Leon Gordon / Leon Gordan Miller FIDSA P. Pres. I.D.I. (ts-open), 084 (Box 92)
  - Nevell, Thomas / Thomas G.W. Nevell IDSA early years - USID, 8/9/80; 067 (Box 92)
  - Noyes, Eliot / Reflections - important - about the period, 033 (Box 92)
  - Parriott, Joseph / Joseph Parriott Early Years ID, 5/1/91; 012 (Box 92)
  - Pile, John / New York IDSA - History John Pile - Monte Levin - F. Giananodo, 6/15/83; 072 (Box 92)
  - Pulos, Arthur / #4 Pulos, 114 (Box 92)
  - Pulos, Arthur / Art Pulos - I.D. Hist. Philly - IDSA, 1976; 034 (Box 92)
  - Pulos, Arthur / Arthur Pulos Interview by Brown Tape 3, 8/20/81; P (Box 92)
  - Pulos, Arthur / Pulos 5 (115), 115 (Box 92)
  - Pulos, Arthur / Pulos Rev. to 1940 - Philly - IDSA Panel, 1976; 035 (Box 92)
  - Redmann, Robert / Prof. Robert Redmann, 4/21/80; 068 (Box 92)
  - Reinecke, Jean / Jean Reinecke Fred Priess - Wards - George Mendenhall - Chi - Dave Painter - Chi Alfons Bach early history (36), 1969; 036 / [056?] (Box 92)
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 1 of 7, 2/91; 102 (Box 92)
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 2 of 7, 2/91; 102A (Box 92)
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 3 of 7, 2/91; 103 (Box 92)
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 4 of 7, 2/91; 104 (Box 92)
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 5 of 7, 2/91; 105 (Box 92)
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 6 of 7, 2/91; 106 (Box 92)